Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955. George Lynes Platt photographs, 1935-1953 (MS Thr 483): Guide.
George Lynes Platt photographs,
1935-1953.
Harvard Theatre Collection, Houghton Library, Harvard College Library, Harvard University
MS Thr 483
Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955.
6 boxes (3 linear ft.)
Photographs by the American photographer George Platt Lynes.
Gift of Frederich R. Koch.
Lynes worked in New York as a fashion photographer for Vogue and Harper's Bazaar and took photographs for Lincoln Kirstein and George Balanchine of the dancers and productions of the American Ballet. He also staged and photographed a series of male nudes.
Arranged alphabetically by subject.
Photographs of fashion models and American Ballet dancers, portraits of W. H. Auden, George Balanchine, Paul Cadmus, Alexandra Danilova, Oskar Kokoschka, and self-portraits.
- "Boreas.", (Box 6)
  Shirtless man blowing fog into the air with opossum, raccoon, and rabbit.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,711.
  Number on photograph.
- "Errante," 1935., (Box 6)
  With Tamara Geva and William Dollar. Geva, wearing dark dress, facing back and wrapped horizontally around Dollar. Dollar, nude, facing front with head bent down, wrapped vertically around Geva.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,970.
- "Mother and Daughter,", (Box 6)
  Nude woman, face obscured, standing with arms upraised at left extreme; [older] woman sits at right in black and white patterned dress. Face in right hand with elbow on knee.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,877.
- "Orpheus and Eurydice," choreography by George Balanchine, New York, 1936., (Box 6)
  Two male nudes dancing with Noguchi sculpture; back reads "Collection of Paul Cadmus."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,617.
- "Picnic at Tintagel," choreography by George Balanchine., (Box 5)
  Seven characters having a picnic at Tintagel; costumes by Beatod.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,701.
- "Sleepwalker, The," 1935., (Box 6)
  Nude man in fetal position lying on a platform; the platform rests on a set of nude legs and buttocks, severed at the hip.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,908.
- Aba, Mata., (Box 1)
  Seated, in evening gown.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,652.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Reaching into trash can, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,600.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Reaching into trash can, facing right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,601.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Leaning on countertop.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,602.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Standing by countertop, facing left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,603.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Sitting on stool.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,604.
- Auden, W. H., (Box 1)
  Holding lid of trash can.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,605.
- Bacon, Thomas., (Box 1)
  Leaning right, against cabinet.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,653.
  Number on photograph: 198-1; Kodak Safety 47.
- Bailey, Bill., (Box 1)
  Shirtless, lying on pillow, arms crossed over head; found with Bill Bailey photographs, but back reads Jimmy Daniels.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,733.
- Bailey, Bill., (Box 1)
  Standing, his right leg crossed over his left, arms spread wide, torso angled left, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,734.
- Bailey, Bill., (Box 1)
  Standing, shirtless, his left hand on the face of a mannequin.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,735.
- Balanchine, George., (Box 1)
  Facing front; back reads "Russell L. has a better one."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,613.
  Number on photograph: 477 14 / Kodak Safety 464.
- Balanchine, George.
  Holding umbrella.
  HTC No.: 22,657.
  Not located, July 2005.
- Balanchine, George;; Magellanes, Nicholas;; Pelus, Marie Jeanne., (Box 1)
  Balanchine in center, wearing suit, not smiling, his arms around Magellanes at left and Pelus at right; Magellanes and Pelus nude, smiling, facing in towards Balanchine and looking out at camera. Printed by Alix Jeffry from a negative by Lynes.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,971.
- Bampton, Rose (?), (Box 1)
  Standing in a meadow, her arms reaching up for the branches of a tree, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,736.
  Number on photograph: LA 207 G-3.
- Baranova, Irina Mikhaĭlovna., (Box 1)
  Standing en pointe, dressed in ballet tutu with flower in her hair, standing situated adjacent to verso of a huge, framed canvas with light behind canvas.
- Beans, Reginald., (Box 1)
  Standing, his right profile, shirtless, eyes closed.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,737.
- Beaton, Cecil, 1938., (Box 1)
  Seated, leaning forward, hands over the bottom of face, looking forward and up.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,888.
  Number on photograph: 742 A.
- Beaton, Cecil, (Box 1)
  Seated, looking down and left, with cigarette and ragged sweater.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,660.
- Beaton, Cecil, (Box 1)
  Leaning against papered wall, wearing ragged sweater and looking down, left, with hands behind back.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,653.
- Bresson, Henri Cartier., (Box 1)
  Seated, with head in the middle of a skull.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,654.
  Number on photograph: 413-1.
- Brynner, Yul., (Box 1)
  Seated, nude, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,699.
- Brynner, Yul., (Box 1)
  Seated, nude, his right leg crossed over to the left, his right arm outstretched and his left arm resting on his head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,700.
- Cadmus, Paul., (Box 1)
  Photo of painting by.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,738.
- Cadmus, Paul,; George Platt Lynes's studio, 1942., (Box 1)
  Asst. Jonathan Tichenor at camera; Cadmus seated on platform, his right hand on his right thigh, his left hand on platform.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,900.
- Cadmus, Paul,; George Platt Lynes's studio, 1942., (Box 1)
  Asst. Jonathan Tichenor at camera; Cadmus reclining on platform, his right knee bent, his left elbow and right hand on platform and his left hand at his chin.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,901.
- Cadmus, Paul, 1938., (Box 1)
  Leaning his head on his right hand, seated, trees in background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,923.
- Cadmus, Paul;; Gish, Lillian., (Box 1)
  Scene in the woods.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,612.
  Number on photograph: 1065-4.
- Cadmus, Paul; and Gish, Lillian., (Box 1)
  In wood; Cadmus in foreground.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,652.
- Calhoun, Rory., (Box 1)
  Seated on table with both hands in pockets.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,655.
  Number on photograph: LA 282 G-8; Kodak Safety 10.
- Calhoun, Rory., (Box 1)
  Seated at table with his left arm and right hand resting on tabletop, watch visible.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,656.
  Number on photograph: LA 282 G-1; Kodak Safety 10.
- Calhoun, Rory., (Box 1)
  Seated on table with both hands at his sides resting on the tabletop.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,657.
  Number on photograph: LA 282 G-7; Kodak Safety 10.
- Carlucci, Tony., (Box 1)
  Standing on beach with three black dogs.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,739.
- Carlucci, Tony, Los Angeles, 1947., (Box 1)
  Seated with legs crossed Indian style, his chin in his left hand, shirtless, facing front; three statue heads in bottom right corner.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,941.
- Carlucci, Tony, Los Angeles, 1947., (Box 1)
  Reclining on couch, shirtless, his left leg crossed under his right leg, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,942.
- Carlucci, Tony, Los Angeles, 1947., (Box 1)
  Seated on table, shirtless, body facing right and looking at camera; four Vogue magazines visible in front of him.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,943.
- Cerolli, Tony, 1950., (Box 1)
  Wearing painting overalls, hands in pockets, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,912.
- Cerulli, Donald., (Box 1)
  In leotard, facing left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,620.
  Number on photograph: 376 20; Kodak Safety 107.
- Chagall, Marc., (Box 1)
  Holding a bouquet of metal roses.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,658.
  Number on photograph: 424-1.
- Chitwood, Teddy, 1937., (Box 1)
  Seated, wearing dark dress shirt and light pants, body facing right, looking at camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,940.
- Cocteau, Jean., (Box 1)
  Seated, looking over back of chair towards upper right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,659.
  Number on photograph: 194 B.
- Cocteau, Jean., (Box 1)
  Leaning on ladder (?) with left hand on frame, another hand (his right?) visible in silhouette..
  HTC No.: HTC 22,654.
- Cocteau, Jean., (Box 1)
  Seated in director's chair, looking up, right; hand crossed at wrist on back of chair.
- Cocteau, Jean, 1936., (Box 1)
  Seated in chair, looking left, his left thumb hooked inside his shirt.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,958.
  Number on photograph: 196 B.
- Connelly, John., (Box 1)
  Lying down next to wall with hands on waist.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,661.
  Number on photograph: 318-6; Kodak Safety 37.
- Connelly, John., (Box 1)
  Lying down next to wall, shirtless, hands on waist.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,662.
  Number on photograph: 318-15; Kodak Safety 37.
- Copland, Aaron., (Box 1)
  Seated in canvas chair next to high wall.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,660.
  Number on photograph: 1313 E.
- Crawford, Joan., (Box 1)
  Wearing dark dress with gingham detail, seated, facing right, her right elbow on her knee and her right hand at her chin.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,963.
  Number on photograph: 17.
- Cummings, E. E.., (Box 1)
  In office, seated on chair with arms crossed, smoking a cigarette.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,740.
- Danilova, Alexandra., (Box 1)
  Posed on cushion, with her shadow on a screen behind her.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,663.
  Number on photograph: 816-3; Eastman-Safety-Kodak 110.
- Danilova, Alexandra., (Box 1)
  Standing next to painting with curtain behind her.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,664.
  Number on photograph: 816-3; 2; Eastman-Safety-Kodak 110.
- Danilova, Alexandra, Hollywood, 1946., (Box 1)
  "Danilova in Hollywood;" Danilova leaning against railing in a foyer with ivy-covered walls; dress by Adrien.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,702.
- Danilova, Alexandra, Hollywood set, 1947., (Box 1)
  Standing in doorway, arms at sides, looking up left; words "(t)rattoria" and "pesce" visible on the worn wall she leans against.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,869.
- Danilova, Alexandra, Hollywood set, 1947., (Box 1)
  On wooden porch, body facing right, leaning back with arms crossed across chest, eyes closed; phrase "Adriaen --- of Amsterdam" visible on wall behind her; three windows at top of photograph.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,870.
- Danilova, Alexandra, Hollywood set, 1947., (Box 1)
  Stepping out of doorway of brick building, body facing right, leaning back, arms raised above head in fifth position.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,871.
- Danilova, Alexandra, Hollywood set, 1947., (Box 1)
  Standing on what appears to be a dock, leaning against railing of boat, her body facing forward, her left arm extended on railing, looking left; lettering on boat reads "BLACK JOKER."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,872.
- Day, Daphne Vane., (Box 1)
  In sequined gown looking up at a woman wrapped in a white curtain.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,665.
  Number on photograph: 686 B.
- de Menecol, Richard., (Box 1)
  In sailor suit and hat; also wearing peacoat with collar turned up; shadow visible on white background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,666.
- de Menecol, Richard., (Box 1)
  In sailor suit with hands on thighs; shadow visible on white background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,667.
- Dewey, Jean., (Box 1)
  Holding pole above head, wearing white scarf, two photographs in his right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,742.
- Dick, Douglas., (Box 1)
  Wearing all white, standing with hands on hips against a bare wall.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,668.
  Number on photograph: 625-9.
- Dick, Douglas., (Box 1)
  Standing with hands on hips, wearing white sweatshirt.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,743.
- Dick, Douglas., (Box 1)
  Standing with hands on hips, wearing black turtleneck, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,744.
- Dick, Douglas, 1947., (Box 1)
  Seated on white floor in empty space, wearing white pants and no shirt or shoes, legs crossed and body facing forward with elbows on knees, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,887.
- Dick, Douglas, 1947., (Box 1)
  Seated on floor, his lower body facing left with legs in front of him, his upper body twisted to the back, with weight supported by his right arm.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,914.
- Douglas, Kirk., (Box 1)
  Reclining by window, looking down.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,964.
  Number on photograph: LA 268G-3.
- Douglas, Kirk., (Box 1)
  Wearing black sweater, looking up and right. Pavel Tchelitchev's portrait of George Platt Lynes dominates background.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,655.
- Douglas, Laurie., (Box 1)
  Opening box in library.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,725.
  Number on photograph. Number on print incorrect.
- Douglas, Laurie., (Box 1)
  Seated on couch with both hands on her temples.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,746.
- Durst, Andre., (Box 1)
  Seated in chair with cigarette, looking left; smaller than other proofs.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,669.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Standing, hands on hips against bare white background, wearing a cap, looking up and left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,747.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Standing, hands on hips against bare white background, wearing a cap, looking down.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,748.
  Folder, no photo.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Seated agains white background so that his right profile is visible.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,749.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Reclining on patterned floor with arms behind him, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,750.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Standing, hands on hips against a bare white background, looking up right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,751.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Lying on his stomach, wearing cuffed jeans, propped on elbows, his head in the upper left of photograph.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,752.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Facing back, twisted around to show right profile of his face, his right leg bent behind him in foreground.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,753.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Facing right, seated on ground, grasping ankles.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,754.
- Easton, Harvey., (Box 2)
  Crouched and facing forward, wearing socks, cuffed jeans, white undershirt, and cap; his right elbow on his right knee.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,755.
- Eglevsky, Andre., (Box 2)
  "Brahms Variations;" dancer, wearing ballet costume, in fifth position, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,703.
- Eglevsky, Andre., (Box 2)
  "Brahms Variations;" dancer, wearing crown, looking up.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,704.
- Eliot, T.S.., (Box 2)
  Contact sheet; various poses in room with bulletin board and American Airlines poster; back reads "Proof. Property of Vogue Studios, 480 Lexington Ave. New York City;" six circled X's on back.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,691.
  Number on photograph: 14251 LA 25 - 14251 LA 36.
- Eliot, T.S.., (Box 2)
  Contact sheet; various poses seated at desk by window; back reads "Proof. property of Vogue Studios, 480 Lexington Ave. New York City;" on back, square is drawn around 14251 LA 37 and letters MW are marked in center; letters MW are also on the front of 14251 LA 37.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,692.
  Number on photograph: 14251 LA 37 - 14251 LA 48.
- Fashion Shot, 1938., (Box 6)
  Woman's face covered by wet paper, her nose sticking though the near-transparent material.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,893.
- Fashion Shot, 1937., (Box 6)
  Sillhouette of woman's head in bottom right of photo, her hair spread over a tree trunk covered in vines which runs diagonally across the photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,904.
- Female Nude, 1953., (Box 6)
  Nude facing back in studio setup of living room, hands clasped behind her; very dark light; photo has wrinkled and browned on reverse.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,891.
- Ferreira, Chico., (Box 2)
  Headshot, leaning against headrest draped with a towel.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,756.
- Flanner, Janet., (Box 2)
  Seated, holding folded newspaper, wearing polka-dot scarf.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,757.
- Fonssagrives, Lisa, 1941., (Box 2)
  Fashion portrait; wearing fur coat, looking left, profile.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,714.
- Ford, Ruth., (Box 2)
  In striped dress, her right knee bent and her right foot on platform, her right hand on her hip, holding cigarette in her left hand, blowing out smoke.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,961.
- French, Jared., (Box 2)
  Reading an anatomy book while seated in front of three illustrations of man's vascular system.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,670.
- French, Jared., (Box 2)
  Holding an anatomical illustration in front of his right side of his face while standing in front of two partial illustrations of man's vascular system; back reads "pajama (group)."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,671.
- French, Jared., (Box 2)
  Standing in front of two illustrations of man's vascular system; wrapped in a poncho and looking down right; back reads "A."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,672.
- Gish, Lillian.
  See Cadmus, Paul.
- Gish, Lillian., (Box 2)
  Leaning in a doorframe in right profile, hair down over her shoulders; 2 relief figures on walls, an orator one with tragic mask.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,658.
- Goyen, William., (Box 2)
  Standing by window wearing all white, with his left hand in his pocket and his right hand hooked over his waistband.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,673.
  Number on photograph: 185-6; Kodak Safety 125.
- Goyen, William., (Box 2)
  Sitting outside of window with arms crossed on windowsill.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,674.
  Number on photograph: 185-3.
- Goyen, William., (Box 2)
  Sitting outside of window with arms crossed on windowsill; his right elbow is slightly farther down on the windowsill than in HTC 20,674.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,675.
  Number on photograph: 185-8.
- Graham, Martha, 1936., (Box 2)
  Looking right with eyes cast down, her left arm thrust diagonally up left across her face, her right arm pointing horizontally across her body to the right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,969.
- Granger, Farley., (Box 1)
  Seated at table with arms crossed on tabletop, looking right; back reads: "Hear you are interested in Kay Thompson act for St Regis think it sensational hear it has doubled [illegible]'s business do grab it if you can love Lynes."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,676.
  Number on photograph: LA 281 G-4.
- Granger, Farley., (Box 1)
  Seated at table, facing front, his left hand in a fist on his chin and his right hand resting on table holding a cigarette.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,677.
  Number on photograph: LA 281 G-5.
- Granger, Farley., (Box 1)
  Seated at table, smiling, with his right arm at a diagonal across his body, his right hand holding a cigarette; damage to proof at lower left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,678.
  Number on photograph: LA 281 G-8; Kodak Safety 10.
- Granger, Farley., (Box 1)
  Seated at table, his left elbow propped on the table and his left hand in a fist at his chin, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,758.
  Number on photograph: LA 281 G-7.
- Granger, Farley., (Box 1)
  Seated at table, both elbows propped on table, his cheek resting in his right hand, looking up.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,759.
- Griffith, Harold., (Box 1)
  Reclining on lounge chair, holding cigarette in hie left hand, his right hand behind his head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,760.
- Grosz, George., (Box 1)
  Facing front with pipe in mouth.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,679.
- Harris, Bill., (Box 2)
  Seated on rock with ocean visible in background, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,761.
- Harris, Bill., (Box 2)
  Seated on pole with rocks and ocean behind, sweater around neck, holding cigarette in his right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,762.
- Harris, William., (Box 2)
  Standing in front of white screen, holding back of filigree chair; damage to middle left of proof.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,680.
- Harrison, Barbara (later Mrs. Lloyd Wescott); Lynes, George Platt, France, 1928., (Box 2)
  At the beach; Lynes holding Harrison in a headlock, both smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,889.
- Harrison, Francis Burton, Jr.., (Box 2)
  Standing to the left side of a large white cloth hanging from the ceiling, his right foot forward, another man's back is visible in the background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,763.
- Harrison, Francis Burton, Jr.., (Box 2)
  Standing amidst strips of white fabric hung from the ceiling, hands on hips.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,764.
- Hart, Richard., (Box 2)
  Sitting on bench in courtyard, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,765.
- Hartley, Marsden., (Box 2)
  Seated behind large concrete slab, with both hands resting on either side of it; in studio of some sort with two men conversing in background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,767.
- Hartley, Marsden., (Box 2)
  Seated on large concrete slab, hands gripping the edges, his shadow cast behind him.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,768.
- Hartley, Marsden., (Box 2)
  Seated in director's chair, umbrella to his right; two men talking in background next to two light racks.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,769.
- Huppler, Dudley., (Box 2)
  Leaning with his right hand against window frame, left thumb hooked under his belt, facing slightly right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,681.
  Number on photograph: 137 12.
- Huppler, Dudley., (Box 2)
  Leaning with his right hand against window frame, left thumb hooked under his belt, facing full front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,682.
  Number on photograph: 137 15.
- Huppler, Dudley., (Box 2)
  Sitting in front of cracked white wall, angled slightly left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,683.
  Number on photograph: 137 17; Kodak Safety 25.
- Huppler, Dudley., (Box 2)
  Sitting in front of cracked white wall, facing full front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,684.
  Number on photograph: 137 3; Kodak Safety 46.
- Huxley, Aldous, 1947., (Box 2)
  Viewed from outside of house, looking out of window, facing camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,933.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  Seated, looking left, hands in pockets, cloud background visible at right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,770.
  Number on photograph: 372-28.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  Seated in chair with both arms resting fully on armrests, looking right, cigarette in his left hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,771.
  Number on photograph: 372-8.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  Seated, his left elbow on armrest and his right arm in his lap, facing forward, cigarette in his left hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,772.
  Number on photograph: 372-12.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  View from the elbows up, looking right, wooden frame fills left third of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,773.
  Number on photograph: 372-6.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  Seated, looking right, his left elbow on armrest and his left hand at his throat.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,774.
  Number on photograph: 372-11.
- Inge, William., (Box 2)
  Seated, facing camera, upper body in shadow.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,659.
- Jourdan, Louis., (Box 2)
  Seated on windowsill, his arms resting on a sawhorse, his right hand over his chin/mouth.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,775.
- Jourdan, Louis., (Box 2)
  Seated on sawhorse in front of window, his left leg spread over the length of the sawhorese, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,776.
- Khill, Marcel., (Box 2)
  Headshot in golden-brown tone with his right hand over the bottom of his face, looking forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,777.
  Number on photograph: 205B.
- Khill, Marcel., (Box 2)
  Seated in canvas chair with both hands on the tips of the armrests, looking left, wearing polka-dotted bow tie; slight damage to upper right edge of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,778.
  Number on photograph: 203B.
- Kinsey, Alfred C.., (Box 2)
  Seated in ornate chair, body facing left, looking forward and slightly up at camera, his left leg crossed over his right leg.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,780.
  Number on photograph: 121-21.
- Kinsey, Alfred C.., (Box 2)
  Seated and facing forward, his elbows resting on armrests and his hands clasped together, light emanating from behind his head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,781.
  Number on photograph: 121-13.
- Kirstein, Fidelina;; Cadmus, Paul., (Box 2)
  Kirstein standing in front of Cadmus; both facing front and looking right; Kirstein wearing large cross around her neck.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,685.
  Number on photograph: 154 12.
- Kirstein, Lincoln., (Box 2)
  Seated, face resting in his right palm, his left hand on his torso, his right leg propped up, looking left; original manila folder reads "Glen Wescott."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,810.
- Kirstein, Lincoln., (Box 2)
  Seated on platform, reclining on his left elbow, his hands clasped, his right knee bent, looking left. Kirstein was director of the American Ballet.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,968.
  Number on photograph: 16.
- Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-., (Box 2)
  Leaning with his elbows against fan, his left hand at his temple, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,686.
  Number on photograph: 105 3.
  Location: Box 2 of 5.
- Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-., (Box 2)
  Leaning with his elbows against fan, his left hand at his temple, looking front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,687.
  Number on photograph: 105 4.